Maybe for you
there's a tomorrow.
Maybe for you,
there's 1,000 or 3,000...
Or ten.
So much time,
you can bathe in it.
So much time, you can waste it.
But for some of us,
there's only today.
And what you do today matters...
In the moment...
And maybe into infinity.
But I didn't know any of that
until right before I fell.
The thing is,
they don't get to know.
You don't wake up with a bad
feeling in your stomach
or see shadows move.
If you're like me,
you wake up
24 minutes and 47 seconds
before your best friend is
supposed to be picking you up.
If you're like me,
your last day starts like this.
Outside at 2:00.
Well, I'll let you know by noon.
Well, I can't organize a playdate...
you want something to eat?
Nope. Good.
Sammy, you like
the bird I made you?
Morning.
Sammy!
What?
You forgot your gloves.
Izzy, how many times do I have to tell you?
Don't touch my stuff.
Go back inside.
It's cold.
Hey, sexy.
Hi.
Get in.
Okay.
I love the sky on
mornings like this. Hey.
Greasy forehead.
Window. Off.
I'm gonna try not to be depressed
because I'm single on cupid day.
That's Valentine's day to you!
Have insomnia
or something, Linds?
- Excuse me?
- It's just cute
- that you get up before us to get breakfast.
- Ooh.
- Did she just call me cute, Kingston?
- I believe she did, Edgecombe.
Al, Linds doesn't do "cute."
No.
- It's not in her lexicon.
- Lexicon? Nice word choice.
Whoo!
Come on.
Seriously?
This was maybe funny the first
bazillion times you did it.
Still funny.
Still is.
Go, baby! Yeah!
No texting and driving.
Don't worry. I'd never let
my best friend die a virgin.
You didn't think
we'd forget, did you?
It's the big day.
Opening night.
Rob texted me. He said, "I
made my bed for you." Ugh!
That is so sweet.
No glove, no love.
You hear me?
Take it!
Take it! Take it!
Take it! Take it! Take it!
Okay, okay, okay. Watch the road.
Oh, my god.
All right. It's fine.
We're fine. We're fine.
Crazy.
We're freakin' fine.
How many roses did you
get last year, Linds?
Twenty-two.
I'm going for 25
this year, though,
and more than one of them
better be from Patrick.
Did I tell you I sat next to Rob
and I had to make him
fill out the request form?
It was depressing.
I'd be happy with 15.
I'm not ashamed to admit it.
Last year, Matt literally
sent me a dozen red roses.
Matt? Oh, come on.
You just spent a whole week crying
in the same pair of sweatpants,
and it got dark.
We're not going back there. No,
I've told you a thousand times.
I'll say it again.
You do not need
that loser. Honestly.
Mm-mmm.
You got your real baes here.
Mm-hmm.
We love you. Come here.
Till death do us part.
Even then.
Oh, get in here.
Mmm. Mmm.
All right, bitches, let's move.
Sisyphus.
Not an std.
What's he like?
What does it mean when something
is described as being Sisyphean?
Does it mean pointless?
Brave?
Late?
Ah... sorry. It was an
emergency in the tribulation.
It was a minor
laserjet explosion.
I hope the printer survived.
All right, back to Sisyphus.
What's his character like?
Does he learn
from pushing that Boulder,
and it...
Hey.
Val-a-gram delivery.
Happy cupid day.
Go ahead.
Relax. It's just roses.
Aw, no roses for Anna.
- That from your boy?
- It's from Rob, yeah.
All right, all right. Keep it down.
Keep it down, people.
Oh, my god!
It's so beautiful.
I'm in heteronormative hell.
Okay, okay, let's hope third
time's the charm. Okay?
Sisyphus.
Back to Sisyphus, class.
Yo, Sam.
Hey.
Oh, man.
Sam. Hey.
Hi.
Did you, uh... did you like it?
What?
Hey, so, um, big party tonight.
Mom is going out of town.
Whoa.
Huge rager, you know.
Why don't you come? Yeah?
I don't know what my plans are.
What everyone else
ends up doing.
See you tonight.
No.
You know the address.
Kent.
You hear about Anna?
- You mean bull dyke.
Please say she tripped
over her nose.
Not yet. But her girlfriend saw the snap
that we posted with her and that girl.
She straight up dumped her.
See?
What?
This is why I deserve
some public recognition
for making shit
like that happen.
Maybe someone should
give me a ribbon.
Like the ones that you used to
have hanging on your wall, Sammy.
Remember?
From horseback riding?
I was, like,
ten years old, Lindsay.
God, Sammy, you were
such a nerd back then.
Okay, but isn't it weird
how that stuff happens?
How things connect
in strange ways.
If Lindsay didn't post that
snap... she deserved it.
I'm just saying, it's crazy now.
I saw this video about chaos
in the universe. Listen.
How a bird flapping its wing in south America
can create a major rainstorm in New York.
Like how one person can watch a
pretentious video about chaos
while three other people
actually die of boredom.
It wasn't a YouTube tutorial, so
you guys wouldn't get it anyway.
- Owie.
- Samantha Kingston.
Hi.
Hey, Rob.
Did you get my rose?
I did...
Who are these ones from?
Your competition.
I wanna see. Sam has no competition, Rob.
You know it.
Okay, well, neither do I. So I guess
we're perfect for each other.
So you're going to that
thing at Kent's tonight?
- I heard he's getting a couple kegs.
I don't know. -Yes!
I'll text you later.
One more.
No, I'm eating.
Get out. Go.
God, they're too cute.
It's gross.
Oh, you guys, tonight our "wittle"
Sammy passes into womanhood.
I'm so proud.
Shh.
I hope you shaved.
Oh, my god.
Don't forget to pee
before and after.
Ah.
Guys. Guys,
sociopath, 12 o'clock.
Oh, god. Does she know
what a brush is?
No.
Norma bates.
Hey, did she get
her val-a-gram?
In chem, I was sitting
right behind her.
What'd she say?
Does she say anything ever?
What'd she do? She tossed
it right after class.
She really should appreciate it more. It's
probably the only rose she'll ever get.
Maybe it had something
to do with the card.
"Maybe next year,
but probably not."
it kinda look like you put it on
your cheeks. It's the same color.
Yeah.
That's the point.
Mmm. Love it.
It's so effin' good.
Can I post this one?
No.
Don't laugh at me.
Okay.
Linds?
Were you nervous
your first time?
I was too drunk to be anything.
Don't freak out if it hurts.
Especially at first.
And don't tense up,
'cause that only makes it worse.
Great. That sounds
really romantic.
Don't worry. It's not like
Rob is some random guy.
You actually like him.
Right. Yes.
So, everyone wants
to hook up with him.
Yeah.
Tonight everything changes.
Mwah. That face.
Baes!
What are you doing?
Fart's house
is actually kind of nice.
If I'd known, I would've stopped
calling him Danny Devito all year.
Sam and you.
I'm gonna go find Patrick.
Will you be okay?
What? I'm gonna go find Patrick.
Yeah.
Mwah.
Hey. Sam.
You made it.
Sam. Sam.
Hi!
Whoo!
Oh, I am sorry.
Let me get that for you.
How drunk are you? I'm not drunk.
Don't worry about it.
You know what?
You're the hottest girl here.
The hottest.
Okay, look, I'm only giving you,
like, an hour, an hour tops.
You know?
You text me and we'll go.
We're just gonna go,
just me and you.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh.
What happened?
Nothing.
I'll see you later, okay?
Elody's really
embarrassing herself.
Elody's a slut.
Lindsay's a bitch
and a drama queen.
I'm rich and have add.
Bae!
Come on!
Oh, get in here, baby.
Patrick, can you go get me
something a little bit stronger?
What's the magic word?
Brb.
Thank you.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Have you?
Yes.
Like in Patrick's mouth?
Oops.
What?
Oh, she's so shitfaced.
No, you're shitfaced, shitface.
I can't believe
high school's almost over.
Well, actually, we did
it right, you know.
Kissed the hottest boys,
went to the sickest parties.
Do you think we'll
remember any of this?
I mean, like two years,
three years from now?
I won't even remember
this tomorrow.
Oh, my god.
What's she doing here?
Up.
Okay.
Hey there, sweetie.
Is that your first drink?
You really should take it easy.
You're a bitch!
Excuse me?
Whoa.
You heard me.
You're a goddamn fetched
bitch just like your mother.
It's no wonder
daddy left. Huh?
You're a bitch too.
What?
You're a drunk.
And you...
You're just pathetic.
You know what? We'd rather
be bitches than a psycho.
Yeah, psycho.
Have you noticed
that nobody likes you?
Psycho.
Did anyone at this party...
Has anyone talked to you?
I don't think so.
You weren't even invited.
That's 'cause you're a freak.
Go back to the ward.
Go home.
Get off me!
Get her off me!
Who are you?
Get out of here!
Psycho!
Get this bitch on a leash!
- You wanna go?
- Freak!
Get out of here!
What the fuck?
Go!
Go back to the ward,
you psycho bitch!
Are you okay?
What the hell
was that about? Huh?
I don't know.
She just called us bitches.
What did she do?
So you attack her?
This is not my fault.
You throw beer all over her?
You know what?
Who are you...
Do not touch me.
Your boyfriend's throwing up in my sink.
You wanna take care of that?
Come on.
Come on!
That was insane.
I'm sorry about Rob, bae.
Music!
Pacific northwest, my ass.
I hate this weather.
Do you guys want to get some food?
I really need carbs.
You sound like my grandmother.
Meow.
Oh, I like this song.
She called us bitches.
I guess we are.
What time is it?
Did you see
that look in her eyes?
- I mean, she just snapped.
- Yeah.
She freaked me out.
Sam, you're 20 minutes late!
Sammy, you like
the bird I made you?
Mommy says you have to get up.
It's Saturday.
Mommy, Sammy won't get up.
Don't make me come up there.
Yeah?
Sexy lady!
- What are you doing?
- I'm so sorry.
I had a nightmare,
so it's like a slow start.
Um, what happened last night?
Oh. Sorry.
I was facetiming with Patrick
till, like, 3:00.
Speaking of which,
are you nervous for tonight?
What?
You, Rob, his flannel sheets?
- I'm gonna shower.
- No. No time.
Come on. It's cupid day.
Whoo!
Seriously? This was maybe funny the
first bazillion times you did it.
Still funny.
Nice tits!
Ohh, I have your present.
No glove, no love.
You hear me?
It goes on him.
Sisyphus.
Not an std.
All right, all right,
keep it down, people.
- It's so beautiful.
- -I'm in heteronormative hell.
Thank you, girls. Thank you.
Okay, let's hope
third time's the charm.
Yo, Sam.
Oh, man.
Sam. You forgot this one.
No, I didn't forget it.
What do you mean?
The more roses you get on cupid day,
the more popular you are, right?
Thanks for the tip,
Kent. Noted.
I didn't say
the rose was from me.
But it is from you, right?
Well, i...
I... anyway, my mom's
out of town...
Out of town and you're
having a party?
Yeah. Do you wanna...
You wanna come or...
I have to go. Well, can
I see you tonight? Or...
What we do?
You're nervous?
No. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
You don't wanna waste the first
night you go full womanhood.
Oh!
Yeah!
Do I look good? I just really don't
wanna look like I'm trying too hard.
You're fine.
Such a weird day.
Like how?
Just weird.
I feel like I'm still
dreaming from yesterday.
Like... or maybe
yesterday was the dream.
I don't know.
You're awake now!
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, my god!
No, don't you... don't... don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna go find Patrick, you guys.
Mwah!
Sam!
Hey, you made it.
Sam. Sam.
Oh, I am sorry.
Let me get that for you.
Rob, I need to talk to you.
About what? What's up?
I'm feeling pranked.
Tonight was supposed to be our
special night. No, no, no, no.
Rob.
What?
I don't feel good.
I'm freaking out.
Always something.
Can we go talk?
Okay, Sam. Okay.
I'm gonna fill my cup up first.
Five minutes.
Can you wait that long?
This room's off-limits.
I was just looking
for the bathroom.
Sorry.
I feel like I'm having Déjà
vu with you being in my room.
Oh, my god. I've been having
Déjà vu all day long.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Oh, yeah?
In Patrick's mouth maybe.
You seem a little guilty.
Were you with Rob, you hussy?
Skank.
Harlot.
Hey, you guys talking about me?
You know what? I think I'm gonna go home.
No, no, no.
No, we just got here.
I'm confused.
I thought you were supposed to
get it on with Rob tonight.
Yeah.
Yeah, I changed
my, um... my mind.
Well, at least I'm not
gonna be the only virgin.
Oh, my god.
What's she doing here?
Watch this.
You're a bitch!
Just like your mother.
No wonder daddy left.
Huh?
You're a bitch too.
What?
You're a drunk.
And you...
You're just pathetic.
Juliet.
You know what?
We'd rather be bitches
than a psycho.
Psycho. Have you noticed
that nobody likes you?
Psycho.
Did anyone at this party...
Has anyone talked to you?
I don't think so.
Go back to the ward.
Go home.
Get off me!
Psycho!
Freak!
Get out of here!
Get the fuck out!
Psycho! Psycho!
Get this bitch on a leash.
Psycho!
You wanna go?
Go back to the ward,
you psycho bitch!
What do you think people will
say about you when you die?
Like I care.
I'm serious.
- That we're hot.
- This shit is morbid, Sam.
Hey, watch the road.
You watch the road.
We need music.
Guys, I'll find a song.
I want to pick a song.
Okay, mom.
Don't elbow me.
Just pick something.
You're trouble.
You always have to pee.
'Cause she drinks too much.
That, and she has the
bladder of a baby squirrel.
The truck.
Truck?
- Watch out for the truck.
- What truck?
It wasn't a dream.
It really happened.
Again.
Sammy, you like the bird I made you?
It's origami.
Mommy says you have to get up.
Tell mom I'm sick.
You don't feel hot.
Stop it.
Let go!
Mommy, Sammy won't get up!
It wasn't until then
that I allowed myself
to think the worst.
Sam?
What's this about
you feeling sick?
I just don't feel good.
On cupid day?
Did something happen?
I don't know.
Did you and Rob have a fight?
No.
Mom, go away.
Please don't use that tone.
I'm just trying to help.
I just need to sleep
a little bit longer.
Please?
Okay. Well, I'll let Lindsay
know that you're going in late.
But I have to be
at work by 10:00.
- Thank you for driving me.
- Sure.
Sammy.
Hmm?
You'll feel better
once you see some of your roses.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Well, you're lucky
to be so popular.
I mean, when I was a senior,
I hadn't even kissed a boy.
Everyone said my eyes were too close
together and that I looked like a fish.
Yeah.
I have to get to work, honey.
I think you're beautiful.
Go.
Bye.
Maybe everything was connected.
Maybe a flock of birds
could cause a rainstorm
and everything done
could be undone.
Maybe things could change.
And maybe I could change them.
It's Rob.
We're having issues.
But it's the day.
The note in his val-a-gram
said, "luv ya."
"L-u-v ya." Luv ya.
What is that? We've been
going out since last year.
Yeah, well, you know, maybe he's just
waiting to say it, like, tonight.
I'm not gonna have sex with him
just so that he says,
"I love you."
I'm not gonna do that.
We go out every weekend. Hmm.
I don't know.
I wanna stay in.
Like we used to.
Okay, but the only reason
we stayed in
was because we weren't invited
to any senior parties.
I just,
bottom line, don't wanna have
to deal with that today.
Okay?
Okay.
All right.
- What are you doing?
- Shh, shh, shh.
What is she...
Don't worry.
Are you texting...
- Oh, my, god.
- That devilish grin though.
Why did he give me that...
What did you say?
Relax.
I just told him that you
got your period. Oh, my...
- That's perfect.
- That's a good one.
- You're welcome.
Lock up the knives and babies!
Does it smell like pee in here?
I can smell her from here.
Why do we hate Juliet?
- Are you serious?
- We don't hate her.
It's just she's super creepy,
with all those weird drawings.
Remember mellow yellow in the fifth grade?
Oh, my god.
When Lindsay found out that
she peed in her sleeping bag
on the girl scout trip.
Why do you care all of a sudden?
You know she should
be institutionalized.
I was just wondering.
That's all.
- So we're going over to your house, right?
- -Obviously.
- Can I borrow something?
- Always. I got you.
Hey. Uh, these came for
you in Daimler's class.
No, I know I'm not wearing
the appropriate attire,
but I promise
they're legitimate.
Cool.
Also, uh, this rose
came for you.
It's kind of like
a painting of a rose.
It stands out
in front of all the others.
Thank you.
Hey, I-i never said
that it was from me.
But whoever it was from, they put
a lot of thought into it, so...
By the way, my, uh, mom
is out of town this weekend,
so I'm gonna throw a big
party tonight. Yeah.
Did you remember the
address or you... hi, Sam.
It was... it was third grade,
but probably don't remember.
But, uh... but do you, uh...
You think you'll come or...
No, I can't. Sorry.
Oh, come on.
Well, I'm... I could have, uh,
crutches on call for you...
Kent. In case you want
to climb up the tree
and play flying squirrel.
That was one time.
Look, I'm just saying,
I'm pre... I'm prepared.
I'm prepared.
Okay, glad to hear it.
So that's a maybe or...
Uh...
I don't think so.
Well, I'll take that "no"
as a "maybe."
So maybe I'll see you tonight.
What we do?
Oh, god.
Juliet Sykes just
arrived at the party.
- Gross.
- Yeah.
The worst. I'm so
glad we didn't go.
Mm. Snapchat alert:
- Rob is totally puking in the kitchen sink.
- Oh, I wanna see that.
Could I see that?
Of course he is.
Ooh, I don't wanna see it.
Gross. Ew.
You kiss that? Mm.
I can't believe you
made this ice cream, ally.
It's literally better
than a restaurant's.
No, it's true. You should go to
cooking school. Screw college.
Thanks, guys.
It has no dairy.
Oh, you're so full of shit.
Thirty-eight.
- You can shut up now.
- What?
Matt's at the party.
Ally, you say "Matt" one more time,
and I will kill you in your sleep.
I will kill you in your sleep.
12:39. 12:39.
I wonder what filter
Terri uses on her photos.
- Major Fomo.
- Such a loser.
Steve's
flirting with a freshman.
I love you guys.
Oh, Sam.
- We love you too.
- Aw.
Weirdo.
Don't go emo on us.
Where's my phone?
Juliet Sykes is dead.
She killed herself.
Then nothing happened
to her at the party.
How totally insane.
Could our rose have something
to do with it?
Don't be stupid.
Imagine how her family feels.
Look, you can't be mean
to someone forever
and then just feel badly
when they die, okay?
We all knew she was crazy.
God, Lindsay, she was your
best friend in fifth grade.
Yeah, you used to sleep over her house.
I mean, you must know her...
Yeah, well, that was before
she became a sociopath, ally.
I'm going back to sleep.
I'm going to sleep in my room.
I'm going with her.
You were friends with Juliet?
No one even talked
to you in fifth grade,
and I don't hold that
against you.
You never said anything.
We made fun of her for all these
years... it's not our fault.
Go to sleep.
I did everything right.
And nothing changed.
Ugh!
The day
starts and ends the same,
regardless
of anything I do or say.
If that's how it works,
I'm gonna do and say
whatever I want.
- Oh, no, you're not wearing that to school.
- My cupid day outfit.
You don't want to give
people the wrong idea.
- What idea is that exactly?
-No, this is not happening.
Go back up
and change, please.
This is my life. I'll do whatever
the hell I want with it.
Dan, can you jump in here, please?
Sam,
it's so disrespectful to talk
to your mom... i don't care.
- Sam!
- I told you not to touch my stuff!
That's it!
You are grounded!
Grounded?
I'm already grounded.
Samantha!
Maybe I was dead and in hell.
Maybe I was alive and in hell.
It didn't matter.
Nothing mattered anymore.
What are you wearing?
Funny.
Excuse me.
Geez, wake up on the wrong
side of the bed or something?
For a few days now, yeah.
You ready?
Hey.
Hi. Sam.
Someone forgot to take her
happy pills this morning.
I took mine.
Well, I know something
that'll cheer you right up.
I swear to god, Elody, if you
hand me a condom right now...
But it's your present,
for your special night.
Take it.
Unless you want to be
a walking std farm.
You would know.
At least I'm not still a virgin.
What the hell is wrong with you?
What did you just say to me?
What is it? Do you feel like you need to
prove to us that you don't give a shit?
Is that what it is?
'Cause guess what. You don't
need to prove anything.
We all know that you don't give a
damn about anybody but yourself.
We're all pretty
fucking clear on that.
What the hell is
your problem today, Sam?
You guys, don't fight.
Just drop it.
- What, you don't agree?
- Leave her out of it.
Why? You're the one who talks shit
about both of them all the time.
"Look at Elody climbing all over Steve.
He doesn't even like her.
Look at ally. Oh my, god!
She's such a know-it-all.
She just loves
the sound of her own voice.
I hope Elody doesn't puke in my car again
and make it smell like alcoholic."
Stop it, Sam.
Out.
Get out!
Now!
I'd love to hear what you say
about me behind my back.
Sisyphus. Not an std.
Don't say it.
I'm in heteronormative hell.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, girls. Thank you.
Okay, okay, let's hope
third time's the charm.
Okay?
Sisyphus.
Hey, what?
You can take 'em.
Oh, Sam, you're breaking
hearts left and right.
Am I breaking yours,
Mr. Daimler?
What?
Your heart.
Am I breaking it?
No, you're not.
My Patience, however,
is at its breaking point.
Take a seat.
Please.
If you insist.
Oh, my god.
Okay. Sisyphus.
Sisyphus.
Why is our friend Sisyphus
still relevant today?
Why's his story
Get this bitch on a leash!
- Psycho!
What the hell?
Shit!
What are you doing in here?
This is my bathroom.
Nice shoes.
Hard to walk in, huh?
I can walk in them
just fine, thank you.
Ah, you need a pair of these.
Comfiest shoes I ever owned.
Really?
All right, your loss.
Whatever.
You wanna trade?
Like switch shoes?
Come on, Kingston. See if I
can get in those without...
Just get out if... hurting myself.
Come on, let's try it.
Why not?
What?
Yeah, let's do it.
Come on!
Why do you guys hate me so much?
I know you know what's written
in this bathroom somewhere.
It's "ac..."
"Equals..."
"BD," right?
Anna Cartulo equals bull dyke.
I mean or maybe it's
"biggest douchebag."
But I reckon that honor definitely
belongs to Lindsay Edgecombe.
So is that it?
'Cause I'm gay?
I don't know.
Isn't that how
it always works out?
There's somebody laughing, there's
somebody being laughed at.
Right.
Look, whatever, really.
I mean, this whole high school
thing's just a blip.
I'm not gonna remember
any of you.
I win.
Do you ever feel like you're living
the same day over and over again
with only like a few things
being different?
Aw, shit, Samantha. You just
described my whole life!
Sam.
Stop it.
Hi, Sam.
You have to ask permission
to talk to me?
Lindsay's just really upset about
what you said. You should apologize.
Well, everything that
I said was true, so...
It doesn't matter if it's true.
She's Lindsay. She's ours.
We're each other's, you know?
Just apologize. You're not listening to me.
I'm not sorry.
Please, Sam?
What? Why do you care
so much, Elody?
Because...
You guys are all I have.
Are you still trying to
turn her against me?
You're the horrible driver.
You're the one who's always criticizing
people and hurting people.
You're the one who lied about being friends
with her and then tortured her for years.
I just followed along,
and yet...
I'm the one paying for it.
Sam, what are you talking about?
Whoa. What?
Oh, my god.
Sam, I haven't seen you in, like, forever.
Where have you...
No!
Get this bitch on a leash!
I love you. Is that what
you wanted to hear?
Sam?
Hey, are...
Are you okay?
I mean, obviously you're crying.
Is there something I can do?
I'll get you a tissue.
Yeah, yeah. Um...
Hey, here.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Sorry I'm in your room.
I know there's a sign.
No, don't worry
about it. I...
The sign's just really for other
people so they don't get my stuff.
It's the first big party
I've ever had, so...
Why'd you have one now?
I figured if I had a party,
you'd come.
I like your room.
Yeah?
It's my dad's old den.
It must get a lot of light.
Yeah. It's like, uh...
Like waking up
in the middle of the sun.
I get to see the old tree.
I like it.
It's... it's constant.
Is that the one
we used to sit in?
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
Do you, uh... do you
remember climbing up it?
And then you jumped down
and sprained your ankle?
I was stupid.
It was very ambitious.
- I should go.
- Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Just stay for a second, okay?
I-I can... I can
drive you home or...
I don't want to go home.
Okay, well, you can, uh... you
could crash here if you want.
Not, not, not like...
Like with me. I...
Somewhere else.
I'll-I'll be somewhere else.
Like bed,
completely to yourself.
The Kent Mcfuller master suite.
Yeah?
Okay.
Hey, it's okay.
Here.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Don't worry about it.
No, I'm sorry...
I've always been so mean to you.
Don't look. Don't read it.
Please? Why? It's...
It's something bad.
Okay.
Your skin's so hot.
It's, uh...
It's always like that.
I wish we could be here forever.
Okay, let's try again.
Hmm.
Aah.
We're taking a day off.
I think you're just
going to drool around.
What does that... and then you're just
going to go through there and end up here.
If I was going to relive
the same day over and over...
I wanted it to be a worthy day.
But not just for me.
Do the kids at school ever make fun
of you for the way that you talk?
Sometimes.
You can do something about that.
You know, you can learn
to talk differently.
But this is my voice. How can
they even know it's me talking?
When I was in the fifth grade,
this girl used to
sing this song...
who did that?
Lindsay.
How come you're so mean to mom?
I'm not mean to mom.
You drew a line on the floor with nail
Polish and said you couldn't cross it.
Mom and I had a fight, and I was mad
at her in the moment, but I didn't...
I didn't think that
she'd actually stay away.
Look at that.
What? That's just the
outside, how pretty it was.
Oh, my gosh. Look at you guys.
Can you send those to me?
Oh! Those are beautiful.
Remember when you used to
come here all the time?
I do. Of course.
Then your daughter
got too cool, so...
- I'm just kidding.
- Can we go watch the pizza?
Okay. Wait, tiger.
I'm glad we did this.
Yeah.
It was just really sweet
what you did today.
Do you think I'm a good person?
Of course I think you're
a good person.
But it doesn't really matter
what I think.
I mean, what's important
is what you think.
No, I'm serious.
I want to know...
Why do you think that
I'm a good person?
Do you remember when
you were a little girl,
you used to take turns riding
all of the horses in the stable
so that none of them
would feel left out?
Do you remember that?
I do.
Mm-hmm.
But I was a little girl.
It's different.
You have a big heart, Sam.
That doesn't go away.
One good thing.
You just focus on
that one good thing,
and you see where it leads you.
How is it possible
to change so much
and not be able to change
anything at all?
I knew I had to do something.
Something good.
Whoo!
You made it.
Oh, sorry.
The room's off-limits.
Oh, forget the sign.
It's no big deal.
That's really just there for other
people so they don't mess with my stuff.
I'm glad you came.
Yeah. I had to.
I like what you've
done with the place.
Yeah. Yeah, this used
to be my dad's old den.
Now it's the, uh... the Kent
Mcfuller master suite.
Yeah, not so good
in the morning, though.
- It's like waking up...
- In the middle of the sun.
Yeah.
I hope you don't think that it's weird
that I'm here with you right now.
Sam, um...
I once wore crocs
for 365 days straight,
so I don't think
anything's weird.
I forgot about your crocs phase.
Yeah.
Why are you always
so nice to me?
Uh, well...
Do you remember in third grade
right after my dad died?
We were in the cafeteria
and I was crying.
And Phil Howe came up to me,
called me a baby,
and then smacked my tray
right out of my hand,
and food went flying everywhere.
I remember what
we were eating too.
It was, um, mashed potatoes
and Turkey burgers.
And you came over,
you scooped up the mashed
potatoes right off the ground
and you went up to Phil and you smashed
the mashed potatoes right in his face.
And you-you then said, "you're
worse than a hot lunch,"
which, at the time,
was a really good insult.
I mean, I didn't laugh
more that day than...
I mean, uh...
It was... it was the first
time I laughed since my...
My dad died and i...
Do you remember
what I said to you?
"You're my hero."
Yeah.
And that day, I-i vowed
to be your hero too.
No matter how long it took.
I'm sorry.
No, don't do... don't be sorry.
It's okay.
Good.
'Cause I'm not really sorry.
Shit.
Wait. I...
Sam! Hey!
Sam! Wait, i...
Oh, my god!
Sam, did you see that?
Hey. Hey, Sam.
Did you see where Juliet went?
Juliet, stop!
Juliet!
Juliet! Wait!
Juliet.
What are you doing here?
I know what happened back there.
Get away from me.
And I feel really bad about it,
and I know this may sound crazy,
but I have a feeling I may be
able to understand you
better than you think that I could.
You hate me.
I don't hate you.
I know we haven't always
been the nicest to you,
but the thing is that Lindsay
didn't mean anything by it.
We didn't know what we were doing.
No.
I used to be friends
with Lindsay.
It was right before
her parents got divorced.
I used to sleep over at her house. Her
parents would be fighting so bad.
She was so upset.
She was so upset
she started wetting the bed.
You remember the name you all
gave me in fifth grade,
the name Lindsay gave me.
Mellow yellow.
Remember that?
You remember the camping trip when I
supposedly peed in my sleeping bag?
It was Lindsay.
Lindsay's the one who peed.
When everyone asked what happened, she just
pointed her finger at me and screamed,
"she did it."
Juliet...
Please let me help you.
It doesn't matter now.
You...
I...
Hey, it's like
your val-a-gram always said.
"Maybe next year, but...
Probably not."
Juliet...
Oh!
For the first time,
when I wake up...
I'm not scared...
Or confused...
Or angry.
Because, for the first time,
I truly understand
what needs to happen.
how to live this day.
- Uh, Friday, right?
- Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
You want something to eat?
I'm good. Thanks.
Lindsay's got it covered.
Mom?
Oh.
I love you.
I love you too.
What, no love for your old man?
I love you too, old man.
Thank you.
Sammy, you forgot your gloves!
What would I do without you?
Hey.
You are perfect
the way that you are, fizzy.
Always remember that.
Oh.
Ugh, I can't breathe!
It's cold!
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Auditioning for a Tampax
commercial? Let's go.
Yeah, baby!
Hey! Hey, get in!
You know how I like it.
Hey, Elody. What, do I have
white stuff on my face?
No. You know
why I love you?
I love you because you're
down for anything. Always.
You know I'm a down-ass bitch.
- You are.
- Hey, I'm down too.
No. Okay.
No, I love you, ally, because
you're curious about the world.
And you're passionate,
and you are driven.
Did someone swallow
Oprah this morning?
I love you, Linds.
I love you because
you're the kind of friend
that toilet papers Jason foster's house
for a week straight all by herself
just because he said
that I was a bad kisser.
Asshole.
Oh, uh, I think I know why
Sam's in such a good mood.
Oh.
It goes on him.
I've been looking for it
everywhere. I can't find it.
Thank you so much for that.
Sisyphus.
- Not an std. -Sorry. It was an
emergency in the tribulation.
A minor laserjet explosion.
Val-a-gram delivery.
- Happy cupid day.
It's so beautiful.
- I'm in heteronormative hell.
- I like your boots.
Sisyphus.
But he still thinks that he'll be
able to push that Boulder uphill.
He's in a prison of his own device.
The only escape is to change.
Be careful.
That.
Oh, man.
Sam. Hey.
Hey.
Um, "you're my hero."
You got a secret admirer?
Secret? That's-that's, um,
not so secret. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, um...
Hey, listen, um, I'm, uh... I'm
having a party tonight. Mm-hmm.
And I was wondering
if you maybe wanted to
come, maybe.
Yeah? No?
What's in it for me?
I... what's in it for me?
Um... yeah.
And, um, I have something I want
to tell you later. A secret.
Later?
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, hey, the "you're my
hero" thing, how did you...
Thank you for my beautiful rose.
I love it.
What'd you say to me?
This is not working out.
Okay, Sam, you can't
break up with me.
I think I can
and I-i think I just did.
I should have picked Elody.
What just happened?
You guys were supposed to...
I mean you said you wanted to...
It's Rob Cokran.
- He doesn't deserve me.
- Nonetheless, very shocking.
Sociopath, 12 o'clock.
- Uh-oh.
- Does it smell like pee in here?
Stop.
Norma bates!
What?
Just don't.
- But it's Juliet.
- Exactly.
It's Juliet. She has a
name and she is a person.
Yesterday you said you were afraid she
would bite you if she got too close.
That was a long time ago.
That was yesterday.
- Hey, Linds.
- All right, let's do this.
Linds?
What?
How come you never told me
about your parents' divorce?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Why would I talk about something
that happened a thousand years ago?
Because it happened to you.
And you matter to me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's go inside.
Come here.
You know you don't have to act
so tough all the time.
Don't worry about me, okay?
Well, I love you no matter what.
Let's get inside.
Move, move, move.
Hey, um, you made it.
Come with me.
What? Uh, okay.
Okay.
I-I-i believe you
owe me a secret, right?
I believe I do.
Okay, so let's hear it.
The secret is...
Yours was the best kiss that
I've ever had in my entire life.
Um, but we haven't...
We haven't kissed.
I mean,
not since the third grade.
Better get started then.
I haven't much time.
Because I wanted to.
Juliet, I need to talk to you.
For a second. It's okay. Please. Actually,
I kind of have somewhere I have to be.
I know what you
have planned for tonight.
And I want you to know that you don't have
to do this, okay? You don't know anything.
I know that you have
something to tell me.
You have something to tell all of us.
You're a bitch.
I have been a bitch.
I have been a bitch. We all have been
bitches. And I'm sorry. I have to go.
I'm trying to tell you how sorry...
I am sorry. You said that.
Sorry, but I have to come with you.
Leave me alone!
I can't.
Sam!
Sam, why did you run away from me?
I can't right now.
You've been ignoring me for
years, and then you kiss me
and then go back to acting... i meant
everything that happened back there.
That's all I can say, that I meant it,
and I wish it hadn't taken me so long.
Are you in trouble?
Uh, you can... you can trust me.
Juliet!
Juliet, don't!
Wait! Wait!
Wh-what's going on?
Why are you following me?
Why can't you leave me alone?
You don't want to die.
You want the pain to stop.
Stop. You stop.
You... you don't know me.
You could never understand.
You have a choice, Juliet.
Not everybody gets that.
Sam!
Please let me help you.
Don't you get it?
You can't help me.
I can't be fixed.
You're not the one who needs fixing.
There is nothing wrong with you.
Don't let anyone
tell you that there is.
This is just a blip. Your
life will change, Juliet,
if you just hold on...
For one more minute.
It's too late for that.
No, it's not.
It's never too late.
Juliet, stop!
Maybe for you,
there's a tomorrow.
Maybe for you, there's 1,000...
Or 3,000.
Or ten.
But for some of us,
there's only today.
And what you do today matters...
In the moment...
And maybe into infinity.
I see only my greatest hits.
I see the things
I want to remember...
And be remembered for.
That's when I realized that
certain moments go on forever.
Even after they're over,
they still go on.
They are the meaning.
Sam?
You saved me.
No.